Warrior. Mother. Queen.
Boudica is a action, war film directed by Jesse V. Johnson.
Inspired by events in A.D.
60, Boudica follows the eponymous Celtic warrior who rules the
Iceni people alongside her husband Prasutagus.
When he dies at the hands of Roman soldiers, Boudica’s kingdom is left
without a male heir and the Romans seize her land and property.
Driven to the edge of madness and determined to avenge her husband’s death, Boudica rallies the
various tribes from the region and wages an epic war against the mighty Roman empire.
Boudica, played by Olga Kurylenko.
Wolfgar, played by Peter Franzén.
Prasutagus, played by Clive Standen.
Cartimanda, played by Lucy Martin.
Catus Decianus, played by Nick Moran.
Old Druid, played by James Faulkner.
Boudica (or sometimes Boudica: Queen of War), is a 2023 British
action drama film directed and written by Jesse V.
The film follows the eponymous Celtic warrior of the Iceni people, Boudica, in Roman Britain and
how she revolted against the Romans after the death of her husband, Prasutagus.
The film stars Olga Kurylenko as the titular character.
The film received mixed reviews.